(Episode 2)
Odajima, what are you messing around for?
Isn't Kataoka dead yet?
I haven't had the right chance.
Get it done.
Before this whole succession thing blows up.
Snatch his territory first.
Boss.
Is he not well?
Forget what I just said.
Forget it.
Just go take Kataoka out.
You're nothing but a tool to me.
If you're a tool, you act like one.
Do what you're told.
Don't you hold a grudge against Kataoka
from seven years ago?
If you understand, then go bring me Kataoka's head.
Odajima.
(Winter 2018)
Wait, hey!
Hurry up!
Are you kidding me?
Stop right there! Hey!
This is bad.
Asahi.
Asahi!
Are you okay?
Asahi.
You'll be okay, Asahi.
Let's go.
We...
Shut up, Asahi.
It's going to be okay.
Of course...
Hey, Odajima.
Yeah.
We're the ultimate duo.
We can do anything.
Let's make it to the top together.
Just shut up.
We're going to the top, aren't we?
Asahi.
Asahi?
No... Don't die, Asahi.
Asahi!
Odajima...
Yeah?
We are...
free.
Asahi?
Asahi!
Why, Asahi?
Why did you have to die?
"The Journey to Kill You"
Is that him?
I see.
Oh, Odajima.
Beer, over here.
Oh yeah, this guy is Odajima.
It's hot, isn't it, kid?
Here, have a drink.
We just met. Are you sure?
Don't worry about it.
- Go on.
- Huh? Can I really take one?
Yeah.
Alright.
You want one too?
No, I can't drink.
I have to drive.
What a buzzkill.
Alright.
Ready? And...
Cheers!
Mister.
So you're walking across the country.
That's right.
I started from the southern tip of Kyushu.
And I'm heading for the northern sea.
That's amazing.
Hey, what's Fukuoka like?
- My mom lives there.
- Huh?
- Isn't Fukuoka in the northeast?
- What?
Hey, hey.
Did you really walk all the way from Kyushu?
Don't look down on me.
I'm a company president back home.
Wow, that's impressive.
You guys, if you ever need a job,
- my company will hire you.
- Oh!
We'll be counting on you then, Mr. President.
And this young lady will be the president's wife.
Oh, stop it.
My husband will get jealous.
Oh, so you're a married woman.
That's even more enticing.
See that?
That big concrete building across the river.
My husband's doing time in there.
A prison.
Nope.
It's a detention center.
A detention center?
He's on death row.
I haven't seen his face in years.
He's refused all visits since he was sentenced.
Twenty thousand yen.
He killed two people.
And got the death penalty
for robbing someone of 27,080 yen.
Not worth it at all, huh?
He's just a guy with bad luck.
The death penalty for killing two people.
Then I should've been executed many times over.
Oh, stop.
Honey...
Why won't you see me?
♪ In the early morning, I'm all alone ♪
♪ Wandering by this seashore ♪
♪ My heart can't help but recall the old days ♪
Miss, you know some old songs.
Well, my grandma raised me.
My parents abandoned me.
Hey, what's this song about?
Miss...
You must have had it rough.
Yeah, but stop it.
That's all in the past now.
Hey, mister.
That's gross! Don't blow your nose on my clothes!
(Sobbing)
Geez.
Oh, I should get to my shift at the bar.
Want me to give you a ride?
Really?
Yeah, and maybe I'll have another drink with you.
Yay!
Hey, Odajima.
Yes.
See you, Mr. President.
Live a long life.
You guys too.
Thanks for the beer.
Bye-bye.
You're quite the bargain.
What's that supposed to mean?
I mean that as a compliment.
Mama-san.
- I brought a customer!
- Huh?
Really?
Odajima.
Nice ass and boobs, right?
I'm not coming back tonight.
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm coming.
See ya, Odajima.
Odajima.
Hey.
It's so hot.
Odajima...
Let's go buy an air conditioner!
Where would we get the money for that?
Of course I know that.
You don't have to tell me.
So hot...
Sir.
Going up?
Odajima.
It's Kataoka-san.
I heard he's only five years older than us.
But he's already the next in line to be underboss.
He's so cool.
- Sir.
- Yeah.
Yes, sir!
- Sir.
- Yeah.
You're too loud.
You idiot.
But Kataoka-san talked to us.
Full of energy, aren't you, kid?
Go buy me a pack of smokes.
Yes, sir.
Keep the change.
Go get yourself some sushi.
Thank you, sir.
How's this, Pompadour?
I look just like Kataoka-san, right?
It doesn't suit you at all.
One day, I'll be the kind of man
who can pull off this look.
The island I was born on...
was so small a child could walk
around the entire thing.
Everyone on the island knew each other.
Whether it was the cars,
the clothes,
or our homes, everything reeked of fish.
I spent every day looking out at the sea.
Is that so?
When I looked at the sea,
I felt like I could do anything.
I told myself,
one day I'd be like Kataoka-san
and make it big.
And then for my mom,
I'd build her a grand house.
Is that so?
And then,
Plus me and...
you have to live with us too.
Me too?
Of course.
You're my family.
Just you wait and see.
Kataoka-san.
What took you so long?
I thought you weren't coming back tonight.
Yeah.
I was supposed to be out all night.
Did she run out on you?
Shut up. I let her go.
She had just taken off her clothes
when she started crying
and said doing this would let her husband down.
What was I supposed to do?
Since the fifth grade,
I've slept with over a thousand women.
But I've never forced anyone who wasn't willing.
So if I say no, does that not count?
If you truly didn't want it, I wouldn't force you.
Right here...
aren't you already biting down on me, refusing to let go?
You're really interesting.
You're always so sullen and quiet,
with that look like nothing in the world interests you.
But when it comes to this, you're unbelievably sexy.
That cold face of yours...
makes me want to pin you down
and take you completely...
ravage you until you're a mess.
Hey.
Um, why isn't it colored in?
Does it bother you?
When you get turned on,
your skin flushes,
and it makes the dragon tattoo
look like it's been colored in.
It's sexy.
Odajima.
You are my tool.
Kill him.
Hurry up and kill him.
Kill him!
Not yet.
There's still...
something I need to know.
Asahi.
Don't you die here.
Aren't we going to make it to the top?
Together, we're going to...
Why?
You left me behind.
Why isn't he dead yet?
Director...
It wasn't Dad.
It was that bastard Kataoka.
That guy Odajima, how many days
does he need to take care of one person?
If we don't find another way, this will never end.
We can't make too much of a scene over there either.
Don't let anyone in the family know.
That Kataoka guy is pretty popular, isn't he?
For a worthless piece of trash who came from the streets.
He's a frivolous guy.
So the younger guys probably find him approachable.
Hey, Kumakura.
Yes.
You know his background, don't you?
Well...
There's nothing about him that
would be of any concern to you, Director.
I'm going to Akasaka. Get the car ready.
Yes, sir.
And get me three women.
Fourth Generation.
This is a critical time for the family.
I urge you to reconsider.
Hey.
- Please hurry.
- What's the rush all of a sudden?
Where is it you want to go?
We're going to take a boat.
Huh?
We're on the run.
Weren't you the one saying we shouldn't take any detours?
- There's something I want to show you.
- And what's that?
This way, please.
You really don't listen sometimes, do you?
What about the car?
We don't need it anymore.
Huh?
It's an island so small
even a child could walk around the whole thing.
That's what I heard.
(Next Episode)
What a godforsaken island.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Please, offer some incense for him.
He used to be one of our family.
And you killed him.
You would know if you were there, wouldn't you?
You're pretty good at putting on an act.
That guy took everything that was mine.
I... should never have been born.
This is the first time I've ever heard
you talk about yourself.
Don't tell me you're starting to catch feelings.
No one knows...
You...
were my first.